Mss.Ms.Coll.115
American Philosophical Society
- Series III. Robert Patterson Kane, 1830-1905; This collection includes letters, letterbooks (1853-1860, legal matters), notebooks on legal cases. Much of this relates to Kane's legal practice in Philadelphia with his father, J. K. Kane, but there is also family correspondence, and much that relate
  Robert Patterson Kane was a Philadelphia lawyer practicing primarily in the Federal Courts, his speciality included patent and admiralty cases. Born in Philadelphia on June 9, 1827, Kane was the son of John Kintzing Kane, a Judge of the Eastern District Court, and Jane Du Val (Leiper). Two of his brothers were Elisha Kent Kane, the Arctic explorer, and General Thomas L. Kane, also a member of the bar. He studied in the law office of Thomas Dunlap and was admitted to the bar on September 18, 1849. Some of his cases include the salvage of the ship "Arcole" and of the Barque "Ferris" and the Morse patent for telegraphic communication. He successfully represented Kockerspergerin a suit against the United States prohibiting his private postal system, known as the "Blood's Dispatch". In the absence of United States District Attorney Van Dyke, he assumed the office. In addition to his work as a lawyer, Mr. Kane took a very active part in the general political contests from 1850-1860. Inheriting from his father the truest Democracy, as he has transmitted it to his son Francis Fisher Kane, he saw with great anxiety the dangers from sectionalism which threatened the country when the Republican party was organized under abolition issues. He exerted himself to the utmost to check what he foresaw would lead to disastrous consequences. Mr. Kane married Elizabeth (Lily) Francis Fisher in 1861. They had three children Eliza Middleton Kane (1863-1952), Joshua Francis Fisher Kane (8/1864-11/1864), Francis Fisher Kane (1866-1955). He died on November 28, 1906.
  Early American History note
  Early American History note The Robert Patterson Kane Papers reflect the career and social life of Robert Patterson Kane, a prominent Philadelphian. The collection is composed of Kane's correspondence (most of which is addressed to Robert Patterson Kane), his legal papers, and his financial records. The bulk of the documents come from the 1850s and 1860s. Also included in the correspondence is an autobiography and family history (called “recollections”) by J.F. Fisher, a member of the prominent Philadelphian Fisher family, taken in 1864.
  See also Series II, VIII, and X.
  Baynard, Edward; Brewster, Benjamin Harris, 1816-1888; Cain family.; Fisher, Joshua Francis, 1807-1873; Green, John P.; Green, Rowland; Grinnell, Cornelius; Guillon, Constant; Harding, George; Henry, Morton P., (Morton Pearson), 1826-1901; Hood, Samuel, 1800?-1875; Hubbell, Horace; Kane, Jane Duval Leiper; Kane, John K. (John Kintzing), 1795-1858; Kane, Thomas Leiper, 1822-1883; Mitchell, S. Weir, (Silas Weir), 1829-1914; Morse, Samuel Finley Breese, 1791-1872; Philadelphia Society for the Employment and Instruction of the Poor.; Taylor, John; Wharton, Geo. M. (George Mifflin), 1808-1870; Business Records and Accounts; General Correspondence; Law; Law firms -- Pennsylvania -- Philadelphia.; Lawyers -- Pennsylvania.; Legal Records; Letterbooks.; Notebooks; Philadelphia (Pa.) -- Social conditions.; Philadelphia (Pa.) -- Social life and customs.; Poor -- Services for -- Pennsylvania -- Philadelphia.; Trials.
  - Papers, 1830-1905
    - Alexander, William, Undated
    - Allen, Mrs. E., 1854 January 3
    - Allingham, Mary, 1819-1828
    - American Philosophical Society Wistar Party, 1850-1854
    - Andrus, W.B., 1851 February 8
    - Bailey, ______, April 10
    - Bailey, W. Swain, 1853 July 9
    - Baily, Joshua L., 1851 August 5
    - Baird, Henry Carey, 1859 January 10
    - Baker and Stetson, 1854-1856
    - Balch, Thomas, 1851 February 24
    - Ball, Marcus, 1859
    - Balmanno, Robert, 1853 June
      With extract of letter of J. Sartain.
    - Barclay, John A., 1855 November 24
    - Barclay, Mrs., February 24
    - Bardy, Rodolph, 1854 February 13
    - Bartlett, W.O., 1852 January 24
    - Bassett, Elisha, 1856 December 1
    - Bayard, Edward, 1862-1864
    - Bayard, F.F., 1857 October 16
    - Baynon, D.W., 1857 October 15
    - Beck, James M., 1896-1900
    - Benton, Stephen, 1850 January 19
    - Bernhisel, John M., 1859 March 30
      To J.P. Green.
    - Biddle, George W., 1852 December 7
    - Biddle, J.W., 1852 February 19
    - Biddle, Mrs. James C., November 26
    - Bigelow, W., 1865 October 21
    - Bireley, Coleman, 1856 April 17
    - Bolivar, George W., 1853 November
    - Bradford, J. Russell, 1854
    - Brewster, Benjamin Harris, 1855, 1865
    - Brewster, F. Carroll, 1862 August 14
      To Furman Sheppard.
    - Brown, David Paul, Jr., 1856 February 22
    - Buckman, Gilbert R., May 14
    - Bucknall, Thomas L., 1855-1856
    - Bulfinch, John, 1856
    - Burton, Stephen, 1850 June 5
    - Butler, Charles, 1851 October 30
      To Thomas Butler
    - Cadwalader, John, 1859 September 24
    - Cadwalader, Mrs. John, February 5
    - Caldwell, N.H., 1858-1859
    - Caldwell, William Pemberton, 1857 October 19
    - Camp, F. de la, 1857 September 28
    - Campbell, A.B., 1848 January 17
      To Rachel Wetherill.
    - Campbell, George T., 1849, 1854
    - Campbell, Theo, Undated
    - Carmen, W., 1850 January 2
    - Carpenter, G.W., 1855 December 3
    - Causey, P.F., 1854 July 8
      To George Wharton
    - Cetti, A.C., 1855 July 16
    - Chaloner, A.D., 1850 May 31
    - Chandler and Ellis, 1854-1856
    - Chase, Caleb, 1853 May 9
    - Chase, Edwin, Undated
    - Churchman, S., 1856 March 25
    - Clark, Thomas W., 1851
    - Cleveland, Charles D., 1850 June 3
      To Managers of the Philadelphia Society for the Employment and Instruction of the Poor.
    - Coit, Henry A., 1881
    - Consolidation banquet, 1854
    - Constable, Mrs. Alida, 1850-1853
    - Cooper, David, 1854-1855
    - Costillo, Thomas, 1850 April 8
    - Crabbe, William H., 1857 October 5
    - Cracroft, Sophia, 1859 March 13
    - Craig, James L., 1851 February 8
    - Cramond, H., 1855 November 29
    - Crooke, Robert L., 1854
    - Curtis, George W., 1857 February 2
    - Cuyler, Theodore, 1855-1856
    - D'Alembert, Alfred, 1853 December 28
      Madeline Phillips. Wedding invitations.
    - David, Jacob C., 1852 May 28
    - Davis, Mrs. Ann, 1854
    - Day, Joseph C., 1872 July 26
    - Dayton, A.T., 1850 May 9
    - DeCoin, Robert L., 1859
      To Sidney L. Kopman.
    - Deloutte, J.A., 1850 April 15
    - Delprat, Fanny, Undated
    - Delprat, John C., Jr., 1850-1851
    - Democratic voters of Bristol, Pa., Undated
    - Dicken, J. Charles, 1872 March 28
    - Donagan, R., Undated
    - Donnelly, Ignatius, 1854 May 30
    - Dougherty, A.E., 1831 June 29
      Return of taxes.
    - Dougherty, George L., 1852 September 18
    - Drayton, W.H., Undated
    - Dunlap, Thomas, Jr., 1850-1856
    - Eaton, H.K., 1856 May 21
    - Ellet, Mrs. E.F., 1865 September 7
      To J.P. Green, in regard to R.P. Kane-Margaret Fox dispute.
    - Engel, Daniel and Company, 1861 November 2
      To A. Dehieff.
    - English, William F., Undated
    - Enterprise Insurance Company, 1859 August 17
      Policy.
    - Evans, Whittier, 1855 November 13
    - Fallow, John, 1852 May 4
    - Female Medical College of Pennsylvania, 1857 November 4
    - First Troop Philadelphia City Cavalry, 1861
    - Fish, A.J., 1855-1856
    - Fisher, Eliza Middleton (Mrs. Joshua) #1, Undated
      Correspondence from Mrs. Eliza Middleton Fisher to daughter Sophia Fisher Coxe, wife of Eckley Brinton Coxe and sister to Elizabeth Fisher Kane.
    - Fisher, Eliza Middleton (Mrs. Joshua) #2, Undated
    - Fisher, Eliza Middleton (Mrs. Joshua) #3, Undated
      Correspondence to Mrs. Eliza Middleton Fisher from daughters Sophia, Elizabeth and Maria.
    - Fisher, Eliza Middleton (Mrs. Joshua)--Will, 1851-1854, 1890
      Mother of Elizabeth Francis Fisher Kane. Will and letters from Lily.
    - Fisher, Elizabeth P., Undated
      Primarily letters from Eliza (Lily) Middleton Fisher, later the wife of Robert Patterson Kane, to her Grandmother Elizabeth P. Francis Fisher.
    - Fisher, George, 1873 April
    - Fisher, Joshua Francis, Undated
    - Fisher, J.F., 1864 April 28
      "Recollections of family traditions...interesting incidents of my own life...contemporary notabilities...and family history".
    - Flanagan, James M., 1856 August 12
    - Forney, John W., 1857 December 21
    - Fox, Margaret, Undated
    - Freeman, Reuben, 1852 July 16
    - Fry, Horace B. and Company, 1852 March 13
    - Gerhard, B., 1851-1856
    - Gest, J.B., 1855 October 4
    - Green, John, Jr., 1873 March 17
      To John P. Green.
    - Green, John P., 1854-1862
    - Green, John P., 1857 February
      To Raven and Bradley.
    - Green, Rowland, 1873
    - Grier, Mrs.
      Contains botanical sketches.
    - Grinnell, Cornelius, 1853-1858
    - Griswold, C.S., 1860 March 23
    - Grubb, William B., 1855, 1859
    - Guillon, Constant, 1854-1864
    - Halsey, A.O., Undated
    - Haly, William W., 1851 April 9
    - Hanson, H.C., 1850 May 3
    - Harding, George, 1850-1854
    - Hargate, John, Undated
      To Mrs. Elizabeth Kane.
    - Hart, John S., 1850 November 22
    - Hart, John S., 1850 November 22
      To Anthony E. Stocker.
    - Hartbill, George, 1850 December 13
    - Hawkins, Dexter A., 1865
    - Hazlehurst, James, 1852 January
    - Heath, Nathaniel, 1852 June 12
      To Reuben Freeman.
    - Heazlett, Charles F., 1850-1856
    - Heilman, H., 1859
    - Henry, Morton P., 1854-1856
    - Heverin, J.S., 1855 December 20
    - Heverin, J.S., 1855 December 20
      To Theodore Birely.
    - Heyer, F., 1849 December 19
    - Hicks, Thomas, Undated
    - Higgins, A.F., 1856 July 3
    - Hilgard, J.E., 1856 April 10
    - Hood, J. Walter, Undated
    - Hood, Samuel, 1852-1856
    - Howe, David, 1857 October 3
    - Hubbell, Horace, 1856
    - Hudson, F., 1849 October 11
    - Hudson, Maria, 1850 March 1
    - Humphreys, Mrs., Undated
    - Humphreys, M.A., Undated
    - Ingersoll, J.R., Undated
    - Ingraham, Miss, Undated
    - Ireland, Anthony, 1856 April 11
    - Irvin and Krebs, 1871
    - Johnston, J.F., 1854-1856
    - Johnston, J.W., Undated
    - Jones, Horation Gates, 1855
    - Kaiglee, Charles, 1851 November 19
    - Kane, Elisha Kent, 1846-1856
    - Kane, Elizabeth, Undated
    - Kane, Elizabeth, 1857
    - Kane, Elizabeth Denniston, 1854-1885
    - Kane, Elizabeth Denniston, 1886
    - Kane, Elizabeth Denniston, 1887
    - Kane, Elizabeth Denniston, 1888
    - Kane, Elizabeth Denniston, 1889-1890
    - Kane, Elizabeth Denniston, 1891
    - Kane, Elizabeth Denniston, 1892-1897
    - Kane, Elizabeth Denniston, undated
    - Kane, Elizabeth Francis Fisher (Mrs. Robert), 1915-1919
      Correspondence to Mrs. Robert P. Kane.
    - Kane, Evan O'Neill, 1896 January 22
    - Kane, Francis Fisher, 1884-1885
    - Kane, Francis Fisher, 1886 January-March
    - Kane, Francis Fisher, 1886 April
    - Kane, Francis Fisher, 1886 May-June
    - Kane, Francis Fisher, 1886 July-September
    - Kane, Francis Fisher, 1887-1888
    - Kane, Francis Fisher, 1889
    - Kane, Francis Fisher, 1890-1891
    - Kane, Francis Fisher, 1892
    - Kane, Francis Fisher, 1893
    - Kane, Francis Fisher, 1894-1895, 1898
    - Kane, Francis Fisher, 1900, 1905, undated
    - Kane, Harriet A., 1885-1891
    - Kane, Jane Duval Leiper, 1854-1861
      See also: Enterprize Insurance Company. Policy to Mrs. J.D.L. Kane, in:
    - Kane, Jane Duval Leiper, Undated
    - Kane, John Kintzing, 1834-1858
    - Kane, John Kintzing, Jr., 1854-1858, 1869
    - Kane, John Kintzing, Jr., Undated
    - Kane, Mabel, Undated
    - Kane, Pierre C., 1850
    - Kane, Mrs. Robert D., 1881 January 31
    - Kane, Robert Patterson, Undated
      Admiralty notes.
    - Kane, Robert Patterson, Undated
      Concerning capitalism and labor.
    - Kane, Robert Patterson, Undated
      Concerning escaped slaves.
    - Kane, Robert Patterson, 1849-1884
      Legal papers.
    - Kane, Robert Patterson, Undated
    - Kane, Robert Patterson, 1888 June 4
      Legal papers, petitions.
    - Kane, Robert Patterson, Undated
      List of pictures at Fern Rock.
    - Kane, Robert Patterson, Undated
      Memorandum.
    - Kane, Robert Patterson, Undated
      Memorandum regarding Julia Reed.
    - Kane, Robert Patterson, 1906
      Obituary from the Legal Intelligencer.
    - Kane, Robert Patterson, Undated
      "Sixth class"
    - Kane, Robert Patterson, 1902
      Transcript of family record from the bible of John K. Kane.
    - Kane, Thomas Leiper, 1846-1867
    - Kane, Thomas Leiper, 1850 May 14
      To Bessie and Pat Kane.
    - Kane, W.L., 1850 November 9
      To J.P. Green, with postscript by R.P. Kane.
    - Kendall, A.W., 1855 December 19
    - Kneass, Strickland, 1857 October 15
    - Knox, John C., 1854 March 25
    - Kopman, Sidney, 1859
    - Kummer, Jacob, 1853
      To Isaac Elliot.
    - Lathrop, Mrs., Undated
    - Law, Edward E., Undated
    - Lehman, William E., 1852-1854
    - Leiper, Cornelia W., Undated
    - Leiper, Elizabeth, Undated
    - Leiper, G.
      To Mrs. J.D.L. Kane.
    - Leiper, Mary T., Undated
    - Leiper, Samuel M., 1833 December 18
    - Leiper, William J., 1854 July 27
    - Leisenring, H.G., 1854 March 8
    - Lesley, James, Jr., 1855-1856
    - Letters to J.P. Green, 1857
    - Letters to R.P. Kane, 1850-1854
    - Lewis, W.D., Undated
    - Lex, Charles E., 1852 May 1
    - Liberty Party of Eastern Pennsylvania, 1850 March 4
    - Lincoln, Charles S., 1851 January 8
    - Lippincott, Joshua, 1828
    - List of persons at work in the house of industry, 1847 March 8
    - List of persons whom clothing, etc., has been given, 1847 March 10
    - Longhead, George, 1856 July 17
    - Lovell, H.H., 1855 July 19
    - Ludlow, James R., 1852
    - Macalester, Charles, 1851 September 15
    - Macalester, Lily, Undated
    - McCall, Peter, 1852-1854
    - McCarlisle, George, 1857 October 8
    - McClees, James E., 1858 March 18
      To C. Guillon.
    - McCready, Malt and Company, 1856 March 25
    - McMurtrie, Henry, 1850 April 19
    - Marsh, William H., 1850 October 17
    - Marwick, Edwin A., 1856 November 2
    - Mason, Charles H., 1858
    - Mathew, G., 1854-1856
    - Memorandum of unfavorable circumstances for R.P. Kane, 1852 January 14
    - Mench, E.A., Undated
    - Mercer, Speakman, 1851 September 1
    - Merrick, J. Vaughan, 1851-1854
    - Metropolitan Fire Insurance Company, 1860 February 4
    - Michael, W.M., 1852 March 17
    - Miller, A.G., 1851 December 16
      To George Plitt.
    - Miscellaneous, 1849-1853, 1859, undated
    - Mitchell, R. Charlson, 1854 July 11
    - Mitchell, R.W., 1858 March 14
    - Mitchell, Silas Weir, 1849-1850
    - Mitchell, S.W., 1853 September 30
      To Alexander Henry.
    - Morgan, A., 1855-1856
    - Morris, Henry W., 1852 February 12
    - Morse, Samuel F.B., 1851
    - Morse, S.F.B., 1851
    - Muller, W.J., 1850 July 6
    - Neal, Charles M., 1856 January 23
    - Neal, William, 1854 June 10
    - Newbold, John S., 1854 June 29
    - Nicholson, Anna, 1850 May 17
    - Nickham, John, 1851 October 7
    - Norris, Thaddeus, and Company, 1854 October 20
    - Northrop, George, 1854 March 10
    - Norton, George, 1855 July 25
    - Our Valedictory, 1846 February 12
      Endorsed by A.D. Bache.
    - Parren, A., 1851 April
    - Patterson, N.N., Undated
    - Patterson, Robert, 1856, 1871
    - Paul, James W.
    - Paul, Mrs. J. Rodman, Undated
    - Penrose, John R., 1856
    - Peterson, Childs V., 1860 July 2
    - Philadelphia Cricket Club, 1858 September 21
    - Philadelphia Society for the employment and instruction of the poor, 1850-1851
    - Phillips, Henry M., 1855 September
    - Phillips, Madeline, Undated
    - Phillips and Allen, 1860 September
    - Phinney, Heman, 1856 November 5
    - Pitt, Joseph M., 1854 February 8
    - Podgers, John, 1855 August 1
    - Porter, William A., 1855-1856
    - Pratt, E.B., 1857 October 12
    - Price, Eli K., 1853 October 17
      To B. Gerhard.
    - Pryor, Samuel, Sr., 1850 July 12
    - Pulzky, Francis, 1852 January 2
    - Raven and Bradley, 1856-1857
    - Rawle, William Henry, 1855 July 9
    - Reed, W.B., 1854 June 19
    - Reed Brothers, 1872 March
    - Rensselaer, J.C. van, 1856
    - Rensselaer, J.C. van, 1859 February 14
      To John Green.
    - Rhoads, James, 1850 April 16
    - Riche, George Inman, 1854 May 27
    - Riley, J. Henry, 1854 August 28
    - Risler, William T., 1855
    - Robbins, Stephen, 1855 September 14
    - Roberts, John, 1852 January 5
    - Robins, George H., et al, 1855 July 10
      Bond to Theodore Birely.
    - Rogers, R.L., Undated
    - Rush, Ann, 1830
    - Rush, Benjamin, 1853-1856
    - Rush, J. Murray, 1855
    - Russell, Archibald, Undated
    - Russell, G., 1855 July 10
    - Russell, John, 1854 July 28
    - Samuel, John, 1856 August 11
    - Sanderson, J., 1857
    - Schofield, E., 1856 December 9
    - Secrist, Jacob, 1850 May 26
    - Seward, William H., 1851 January 1
      To J.W. Ashmead, et al.
    - Sheppard, F., 1854 August 25
    - Sherman, William P., 1852 April 28
    - Shields, Charles, 1866 February 12
    - Smith, Thomas S., 1858 May 6
    - Sonder, B. Rush, Undated
    - Souder, Edmond A., 1854-1856
    - Spencer, J.A., 1852 April 1
    - Sproston, Mary, 1857 September 25
    - Stenhouse, B.H., 1858 July 2
    - Stetler, William, 1856 July 4
    - Stetson, D.S., 1855-1856
    - Stevens, Mrs. John A., Undated
    - Stovell, Fred, 1857-1859
    - Sulger, Isaac, 1855
    - Swabel, John H., 1857 October 14
    - Taylor, B.B., 1854 October 2
    - Taylor, James, 1849 October 29
    - Taylor, John, 1855-1856
    - Taylor, Robert, 1859 March 30
      Deceased. Account...
    - Tennent, M.A., Undated
    - Thomas, A.G., Undated
    - Thomas, John H., 1854
    - Thompson, Isabel P., Undated
    - Titus, John, 1855 November 1
    - Tucker, St. George, 1860-1862
      Materials...
    - United States. Secretary of the Navy., 1850 November 13
    - Van der Kemp, Mrs., Undated
    - Van Dyke, J.C., 1856 July 5
    - Vansart, Joshua, 1857 February 28
    - Van Wyck, C.C., 1846 November 6
    - Vezin, Charles, 1856 April 26
    - Vicker, George, 1852 March 3
    - Vincent, Mrs., Undated
    - Wallace and Fielding, 1872 June 20
    - Waln, Edward, 1852 January 29
    - Ward, Charlotte M., 1858 March 10
    - Watson, James C., 1857 August 10
    - Weaver, William H., 1846-1849
    - Wharton, G.M., 1854-1857
    - Wharton, G.M., 1856 April 18
    - Wharton, Henry, 1855
      Contains sketches, poetry.
    - Wheaton, George, 1855 May 1
    - White, Edward W., Undated
    - White, H.M., 1850 April 20
    - Willeby, Samuel, 1856 April 12
    - Williams, Henry I., 1847 August 19
    - Winthrop, Charles Francis, 1851, 1854
    - Winthrop, Francis, 1851 July 10
    - Wister, William Rotch, 1854 August 30
    - Wister, William and R.P. Kane, 1854 September 7
      To Myers, Claghorne and Company.
    - Wolf, Jacob, 1854 October 8
    - Wollaston, G.W., 1850 August 23
    - Wood, C.M., Undated
      To J.P. Green; To Aunt Kane.
    - Wood, J. Walter, 1852-1853
    - Wood, J. Walter, 1857
      To J.K. Kane.
    - Wood, William, 1849 November 2
    - Wyeth, John, 1857 March 21
    - Young, George, 1856 November 10
  - Letterbook, 1860-1861
    - Badger, William, 1861 March 23
    - Bertram, George, 1860 December 29
    - Blanchard, Sherman and Company, 1861 March 25
    - Blind, managers of the, 1861 January 3
    - Brewster, Benjamin N., 1860 November 12
    - Brewster, J. Carroll, 1861 June 10
    - Carroll, William J., 1860 December 31
    - Cone, Brinton, 1860
    - Crocker, Henry, 1861
    - Curtis, Franklin, 1860 November 28
    - DaCosta, Charles M., 1861 January 2
    - Dehuff, Abraham, 1861
    - Donagan, Richard, 1860 December 1
    - Dougherty, Daniel, 1861 February 12
    - Fallon and Ferrill, 1861 March 23
    - Gerhard, B., 1860 November 30
    - Green, Arthur N., 1860-1861
    - Grier, R.C., 1861
    - Henry, M. P., 1861
    - Hollister, William H., 1860-1861
    - Husbands, C.M., 1861 February 25
    - Jones, B.M., 1861 February 8
    - Kane, Thomas Leiper, 1860 October 3
    - Kelley, William D., 1861 January 11
    - Kurtz, Henry C., 1860 November 28
    - McCool, I.A., 1861
    - McKean and Elk Land and Improvement Company, 1861
    - Middleton, D.W., 1861 February 15
    - Moore, M., 1860 November 18
    - Osbourne, A., 1861 January 20
    - Patents, Commissioner of, 1860 November 24
    - Paxson, Edward M., 1860
    - Penrose, Jonathan R., 1860 November 9
    - Phillips, Henry M., 1861 February 26
    - Plitt, George, 1861 February 26
    - Plitt, S.W., 1861 February 25
    - Quinn, William, 1861 February 15
    - Reed, William B., Undated
    - Rutter, Newhall and Company, 1861 February 14
    - Sampson and Tappan, 1861 March 20
    - Serrill, J.S., 1861 January 1
    - Sibley, Reuben, 1860 December 19
    - Souder, E.A. and Company, 1861 March 5
    - Stevens, Jonathan L., 1860 December 27
    - Stone, James W., 1860 November 21
    - Stroud, George M., 1861 January 7
    - Tucker, St. George, 1861
    - VanDyke, James C., 1860 November 20
    - Wetherill, Jonathan R., 1861 January 15
    - Wharton, George M., 1860 November 27
    - Wood and Redmond, 1861 January 1
    - Wood, J. Walter, 1861 March 9
    - Young, George, 1861
  - Letterbook #7, 1858-1860
    - Adams, Bery P., 1858-1859
    - AlBurtis, E.K., 1859
    - Alexander, William, Undated
    - Ashton, J. Hubley, 1859 May 11
    - Backus, I. Trumbell, Undated
    - Baker, I. and Company, 1858
    - Bascom, Joseph M., 1858 October 6
    - Bayard, J.J., 1859 October 28
    - Beckett, Thomas J., 1858 December 15
    - Biddle, George W., 1858
    - Biddle, William, 1858-1859
    - Blanchard, Sherman and Company, 1859
    - Bradford, J. Russell, 1858
    - Brady, M.B., 1858
    - Brewster, B.H., 1859
    - Brown, David Paul, 1858 March 30
    - Burrill, Charles D., 1858 September 8
    - Burrill, Davidson, Burrill, 1859
    - Cabot, Joseph, 1859
    - Carroll, William Thomas, 1859
    - Chace, Celeb, 1859 February 8
    - Chace, Edward, 1858
    - Chandler and Delaplain, 1858 December 8
    - Chandler and Ellis, 1858
    - Church, Second Presbyterian, 1859 March 21
    - Clark, Albert, 1858 December 14
    - Clay, Joseph A., 1859 January 25
    - Clendaniel, J., 1858 October 8
    - Cobb, Charles K., 1859 March 2
    - Cone, J., 1859 February 7
    - Conroy, P.W., 1859 December 17
    - Constable, A.V.R., 1858-1859
    - Coxe, Charles W., 1859 May 6
    - Cramp, Charles H., 1859 September 5
    - Curtis, Franklin, 1858-1859
    - Cuyler, Theo, Undated
    - DaCosta, Charles M., 1859-1860
    - DaCosta, J., Undated
    - Davis, Ann, 1859
    - Dayson, Joseph, 1859 September 28
    - DeGrott, Anna R., 1859 November 7
    - DeLamano, W., 1859 February 7
    - Devereux, Richard G., 1858 July 26
    - Dodd, Joseph, 1858 August 3
    - Dougherty, Daniel, 1858 November 13
    - Duffield, C.B., 1858 June 7
    - Dungleson, R., 1859 September 26
    - Dunlap, Y., 1859
    - Enterprise Insurance Company, 1858 May 7
    - Fallon and Serrill, 1858-1859
    - Gerhard, Benjamin, 1858 October 6
    - Gibbons, Charles, 1858
    - Goodwin, C., Undated
    - Gray, H.J., 1858 December 4
    - Grinnell, C., 1859
    - Grinnell, Henry, 1858 May 27
    - Gummey, John M., 1859 June 10
    - Hale, R.C., Undated
    - Hammitt, John, 1859 November 16
    - Harb, J.S., 1858
    - Havard, Charles, 1858
    - Havard and Company, 1858
    - Heazlitt, C.F., 1858-1859
    - Henczenberger, William, 1859 May 23
    - Henry, M.P., Undated
    - Hicks, Thomas, 1859 November 3
    - Hirst, Lucas, 1858 October 25
    - Hobson, George G., 1858 May